export const WORDS = [
    {back: "tunnag", front: "duck", level: "Intro"},
{back: "snog", front: "nice", level: "Intro"},
{back: "seo", front: "This is", level: "Intro"},
{back: "piseag", front: "kitten", level: "Intro"},
{back: "muc", front: "pig", level: "Intro"},
{back: "Mòrag", front: "Morag", level: "Intro"},
{back: "mòr", front: "big", level: "Intro"},
{back: "math", front: "good", level: "Intro"},
{back: "Irn bru", front: "Irn Bru", level: "Intro"},
{back: "Iain", front: "John", level: "Intro"},
{back: "gàidhlig", front: "Gaelic", level: "Intro"},
{back: "Eilidh", front: "Helen", level: "Intro"},
{back: "dona", front: "bad", level: "Intro"},
{back: "cù", front: "dog", level: "Intro"},
{back: "cearc", front: "chicken", level: "Intro"},
{back: "cat", front: "cat", level: "Intro"},
{back: "caraid", front: "friend", level: "Intro"},
{back: "Calum", front: "Calum", level: "Intro"},
{back: "caileag", front: "girl", level: "Intro"},
{back: "bò", front: "cow", level: "Intro"},
{back: "beag", front: "little", level: "Intro"},
{back: "balach", front: "boy", level: "Intro"},
{back: "Anna", front: "Anne", level: "Intro"},
{back: "agus", front: "and", level: "Intro"},
{back: "uisge-beatha", front: "Whisky", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "uisge", front: "Water", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "taigeis", front: "haggis", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "sin", front: "that", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "sgadan", front: "herring", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "seo", front: "this", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "salann", front: "salt", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "rìs", front: "rice", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "piobar", front: "pepper", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "is toil leam", front: "I like", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "ìm", front: "butter", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "idir", front: "at all", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "iasg", front: "fish", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "hama", front: "hama", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "guga", front: "guga", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "cha toil leam", front: "I do not like", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "cèic", front: "cake", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "càise", front: "cheese", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "buntàta", front: "potato", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "brot", front: "soup", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "brochan", front: "porridge", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "blasta", front: "tasty", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "biadh", front: "food", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "aran", front: "bread", level: "Food and Drink"},
{back: "tìoraidh", front: "cheerio", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "tì", front: "tea", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "tapadh leibh", front: "thank you (formal)", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "tapadh leat", front: "thank you (informal)", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "slàinte", front: "cheers/health", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "siùcar", front: "sugar", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "sgoinneil", front: "great", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "ollaimh", front: "professor", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "oidhche mhath", front: "good night", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "oidhche", front: "night", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "madainn mhath", front: "good morning", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "leat", front: "with you (le)", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "Iseabail", front: "Isabella", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "halò", front: "hello", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "feasgar math", front: "good afternoon", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "fàilte", front: "welcome", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "Eilidh", front: "Helen", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "Ealasaid", front: "Elizabeth", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "cofaidh", front: "coffee", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "ceud mìle fàilte", front: "one hundred thousand welcomes", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "bainne", front: "milk", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "athair", front: "father", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "Anndra", front: "Andrew", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "Anna", front: "Anne", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "a thidseir", front: "teacher (vocative)", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "a sheanair", front: "grandfather (vocative)", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "a phiuthar", front: "sister (vocative)", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "a mhàthair", front: "mother (vocative)", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "a charaid", front: "friend (vocative)", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "a bhràthair", front: "brother (vocative)", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "a bhalaich", front: "boy (vocative)", level: "Phrases"},
{back: "toilichte", front: "happy", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "thu", front: "you (informal)", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "spòrsail", front: "fun", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "sibh", front: "you (formal)", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "sgìth", front: "tired", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "Seumas", front: "James", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "mi", front: "me", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "iseabail", front: "Isabella", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "i", front: "she", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "gu math", front: "well", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "gabh mo leisgeul", front: "excuse me", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "e", front: "he", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "duilich", front: "sorry", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "crosta", front: "cross", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "ciamar a tha", front: "how is...", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "cho", front: "so", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "ceart gu leòr", front: "all right", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "brònach", front: "sad", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "Anndra", front: "Andrew", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "a-nis", front: "now", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "air bhioran", front: "excited", level: "Feelings"},
{back: "trang", front: "busy", level: "About Me"},
{back: "steòrnabhagh", front: "Stornoway", level: "About Me"},
{back: "Seòras", front: "George", level: "About Me"},
{back: "sasainn", front: "England", level: "About Me"},
{back: "muile", front: "Mull", level: "About Me"},
{back: "mòr", front: "big", level: "About Me"},
{back: "Màiri", front: "Mary", level: "About Me"},
{back: "lunnainn", front: "London", level: "About Me"},
{back: "leòdhas", front: "Lewis", level: "About Me"},
{back: "inbhir nis", front: "Inverness", level: "About Me"},
{back: "ìle", front: "Islay", level: "About Me"},
{back: "Iain", front: "John", level: "About Me"},
{back: "glaschu", front: "Glasgow", level: "About Me"},
{back: "èirinn", front: "Ireland", level: "About Me"},
{back: "dùn èideann", front: "Edinburgh", level: "About Me"},
{back: "dùn", front: "Dun", level: "About Me"},
{back: "cò", front: "Who", level: "About Me"},
{back: "canada", front: "Canada", level: "About Me"},
{back: "barraigh", front: "Barra", level: "About Me"},
{back: "alba nuadh", front: "Nova Scotia", level: "About Me"},
{back: "alba", front: "Scotland", level: "About Me"},
{back: "àlainn", front: "beautiful", level: "About Me"},
{back: "aimearaga", front: "America", level: "About Me"},
{back: "orm", front: "on me", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "lèine", front: "shirt", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "lèine-t", front: "t-shirt", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "sgiort", front: "skirt", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "bròg", front: "shoe", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "seall", front: "look", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "briogais", front: "trousers", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "bòtannan", front: "boots", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "còta", front: "coat", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "ort", front: "on you", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "bonaid", front: "bonnet", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "drathais", front: "pants", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "ag iarraidh", front: "wanting", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "a' ceannach", front: "buying", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "dreasa", front: "dress", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "speuclairean", front: "glasses", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "geansaidh", front: "jumper", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "uaireadair", front: "watch", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "sinn", front: "we", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "iad", front: "they", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "stocainnean", front: "socks", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "fèileadh", front: "kilt", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "aodach", front: "clothing", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "seacaid", front: "jacket", level: "Clothing"},
{back: "agam", front: "at me", level: "Pets"},
{back: "luch", front: "mouse", level: "Pets"},
{back: "eun", front: "a bird", level: "Pets"},
{back: "cuilean", front: "puppy", level: "Pets"},
{back: "brèagha", front: "pretty", level: "Pets"},
{back: "peata", front: "pet", level: "Pets"},
{back: "agad", front: "at you", level: "Pets"},
{back: "uan", front: "lamb", level: "Pets"},
{back: "each", front: "horse", level: "Pets"},
{back: "caora", front: "sheep", level: "Pets"},
{back: "glè mhath", front: "very good", level: "Pets"},
{back: "glè bheag", front: "very small", level: "Pets"},
{back: "glè", front: "very", level: "Pets"},
{back: "losgann", front: "frog", level: "Pets"},
{back: "àrd", front: "high", level: "Pets"},
{back: "òg", front: "young", level: "Pets"},
{back: "èibhinn", front: "funny", level: "Pets"},
{back: "gòrach", front: "stupid", level: "Pets"},
{back: "a' faicinn", front: "seeing", level: "Pets"},
{back: "a' cluinntinn", front: "hearing", level: "Pets"},
{back: "damhan-allaidh", front: "spider", level: "Pets"},
{back: "radan", front: "rat", level: "Pets"},
{back: "coineanach", front: "rabbit", level: "Pets"},
{back: "gobhar", front: "goat", level: "Pets"},
{back: "fliuch", front: "wet", level: "Weather"},
{back: "fuar", front: "cold", level: "Weather"},
{back: "gaothach", front: "Windy", level: "Weather"},
{back: "blàth", front: "warm", level: "Weather"},
{back: "grianach", front: "sunny", level: "Weather"},
{back: "ceòthach", front: "misty", level: "Weather"},
{back: "garbh", front: "rough", level: "Weather"},
{back: "bheil", front: "Is", level: "Weather"},
{back: "a-muigh", front: "outward", level: "Weather"},
{back: "a' faireachdainn", front: "Feeling", level: "Weather"},
{back: "sgòthach", front: "Cloudy", level: "Weather"},
{back: "gu math", front: "well", level: "Weather"},
{back: "dorcha", front: "dark", level: "Weather"},
{back: "cuidich mi", front: "help me", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "slàinte mhath", front: "Good health", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "dè tha dol", front: "what's up", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "a chàirdean", front: "friends (vocative)", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "tìoraidh an-dràsta", front: "cheerio now", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "dè", front: "what", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "a-rithist", front: "again", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "mòran taing", front: "many thanks", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "'s e do bheatha", front: "you're welcome", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "feumaidh mi falbh", front: "I have to go", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "na gabh dragh", front: "never mind", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "a' tuigsinn", front: "Understanding", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "bruidhinn nas slaodaiche", front: "talk more slowly", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "can sin a-rithist", front: "say that again", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "mar sin leat", front: "goodbye", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "beatha", front: "Life", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "dè an t-ainm a th' ort", front: "what's your name", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "cailean", front: "Colin", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "beathag", front: "Beth", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "raonaid", front: "Rachel", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "ainm", front: "Name", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "Dòmhnall", front: "Donald", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "cuideachd", front: "Also", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "obh obh", front: "oh no", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "runrig", front: "Runrig", level: "Phrases 2"},
{back: "an t-uisge", front: "the rain", level: "Rain etc."},
{back: "sneachd", front: "Snow", level: "Rain etc."},
{back: "reòthadh", front: "ice", level: "Rain etc."},
{back: "ach", front: "But", level: "Rain etc."},
{back: "dealanaich", front: "lightning", level: "Rain etc."},
{back: "tàirneanaich", front: "thunder", level: "Rain etc."},
{back: "fhathast", front: "still", level: "Rain etc."},
{back: "no", front: "or", level: "Rain etc."},
{back: "an-dràsta", front: "right now", level: "Rain etc."},
{back: "an-diugh", front: "today", level: "Rain etc."},
{back: "cò ris a tha an t-sìde coltach", front: "What is the weather like", level: "Rain etc."},
{back: "aon chù", front: "one dog", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "bàta", front: "boat", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "aon bhàta", front: "one boat", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "aon chàr", front: "one car", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "bus", front: "bus", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "aon bhus", front: "one bus", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "càr", front: "car", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "aon", front: "one", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "cia mheud", front: "how many", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "asal", front: "donkey", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "eala", front: "Swan", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "uinneag", front: "Window", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "dà", front: "two", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "òran", front: "a song", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "dà chàr", front: "Two cars", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "dà bhus", front: "Two buses", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "dà mhuc", front: "Two pigs", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "dà phiseag", front: "two kittens", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "dà chù", front: "Two dogs", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "dà chat", front: "Two cats", level: "Numbers"},
{back: "bràthair", front: "brother", level: "Family"},
{back: "aon bhràthair", front: "one brother", level: "Family"},
{back: "bràithrean", front: "Brothers", level: "Family"},
{back: "piuthar", front: "sister", level: "Family"},
{back: "aon phiuthar", front: "one sister", level: "Family"},
{back: "seanair", front: "grandfather", level: "Family"},
{back: "athair", front: "father", level: "Family"},
{back: "mac", front: "son", level: "Family"},
{back: "teaghlach", front: "family", level: "Family"},
{back: "leanabh", front: "a child", level: "Family"},
{back: "peathraichean", front: "Sisters", level: "Family"},
{back: "bean", front: "Wife", level: "Family"},
{back: "seanmhair", front: "grandmother", level: "Family"},
{back: "nighean", front: "daughter", level: "Family"},
{back: "màthair", front: "mother", level: "Family"},
{back: "ainmeil", front: "famous", level: "Family"},
{back: "antaidh", front: "Aunt", level: "Family"},
{back: "uncail", front: "uncle", level: "Family"},
{back: "an duine agam", front: "my husband", level: "Family"},
{back: "againn", front: "at us", level: "Family"},
{back: "clann", front: "children", level: "Family"},
{back: "luath", front: "quick", level: "Family"},
{back: "reamhar", front: "fat", level: "Family"},
{back: "onarach", front: "honest", level: "Family"},
{back: "sgriosail", front: "horrible", level: "Family"},
{back: "laghach", front: "nice", level: "Family"},
{back: "neònach", front: "weird", level: "Family"},
{back: "leabhar", front: "a book", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "rathad", front: "Road", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "sgian", front: "a knife", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "sgillinn", front: "a penny", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "stais", front: "moustache", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "latha", front: "day", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "smiogaid", front: "chin", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "not", front: "pound", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "trì", front: "three", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "ceithir", front: "four", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "còig", front: "five", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "sia", front: "six", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "bàtaichean", front: "boats", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "mucan", front: "pigs", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "piseagan", front: "kittens", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "seachd", front: "seven", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "ochd", front: "eight", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "naoi", front: "nine", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "deich", front: "ten", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "coin", front: "dogs", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "cait", front: "cats", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "a' faighinn", front: "getting", level: "Numbers 2"},
{back: "sùgh", front: "juice", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "leann", front: "beer", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "sùbh-làir", front: "strawberry", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "uachdar", front: "cream", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "suiteas", front: "sweeties", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "fìon", front: "Wine", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "mions", front: "mini", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "botal", front: "bottle", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "brot", front: "soup", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "paidh", front: "pie", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "ubhal", front: "apple", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "orainsear", front: "orange", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "isbean", front: "sausage", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "aran", front: "bread", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "ìm", front: "butter", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "bu toil leam", front: "i would like", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "ag ithe", front: "eating", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "snèap", front: "turnip", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "reòiteag", front: "ice cream", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "biadh", front: "Food", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "ugh", front: "an egg", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "ag òl", front: "drinking", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "cha bu toil leam", front: "i wouldn't like", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "glè bhlasta", front: "very tasty", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "tomàto", front: "tomonto", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "uinnean", front: "onion", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "curran", front: "carrot", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "òl", front: "drink", level: "Food 2"},
{back: "aig", front: "at", level: "Colors"},
{back: "geal", front: "White", level: "Colors"},
{back: "dubh", front: "black", level: "Colors"},
{back: "orains", front: "Orange", level: "Colors"},
{back: "purpaidh", front: "purple", level: "Colors"},
{back: "ùr", front: "new", level: "Colors"},
{back: "e", front: "he", level: "Colors"},
{back: "pinc", front: "pink", level: "Colors"},
{back: "dearg", front: "Red", level: "Colors"},
{back: "gorm", front: "blue", level: "Colors"},
{back: "feumaidh mi", front: "I need", level: "Colors"},
{back: "feumaidh tu", front: "You need", level: "Colors"},
{back: "buidhe", front: "yellow", level: "Colors"},
{back: "glas", front: "Gray", level: "Colors"},
{back: "uaine", front: "green", level: "Colors"},
{back: "donn", front: "Brown", level: "Colors"},
{back: "liath", front: "gray", level: "Colors"},
{back: "briogais ghoirid", front: "Short trousers", level: "Colors"},
{back: "putan", front: "button", level: "Colors"},
{back: "goirid", front: "short", level: "Colors"},
{back: "gu leòr", front: "enough", level: "Colors"},
{back: "fada", front: "long", level: "Colors"},
{back: "a' dèanamh", front: "doing", level: "Colors"},
{back: "crios", front: "belt", level: "Colors"},
{back: "a' goid", front: "stealing", level: "Colors"},
{back: "a' cumail", front: "keeps", level: "Colors"},
{back: "deise", front: "suit", level: "Colors"},
{back: "eile", front: "else", level: "Colors"},
{back: "taigh", front: "house", level: "Home"},
{back: "gàrradh", front: "garden", level: "Home"},
{back: "coimpiutair", front: "computer", level: "Home"},
{back: "an toil leat", front: "do you like", level: "Home"},
{back: "deasg", front: "desk", level: "Home"},
{back: "iuchair", front: "Key", level: "Home"},
{back: "flat", front: "flat", level: "Home"},
{back: "bòrd", front: "table", level: "Home"},
{back: "preas", front: "cupboard", level: "Home"},
{back: "mapa", front: "Map", level: "Home"},
{back: "dealbh", front: "picture", level: "Home"},
{back: "soitheach", front: "plate", level: "Home"},
{back: "amar", front: "bath", level: "Home"},
{back: "eadar-lìon", front: "Internet", level: "Home"},
{back: "òrd", front: "hammer", level: "Home"},
{back: "aca", front: "at them", level: "Home"},
{back: "seòmar-cadail", front: "bedroom", level: "Home"},
{back: "sin", front: "that", level: "Home"},
{back: "aige", front: "at him", level: "Home"},
{back: "taigh-beag", front: "toilet", level: "Home"},
{back: "frids", front: "fridge", level: "Home"},
{back: "balla", front: "wall", level: "Home"},
{back: "seo", front: "this", level: "Home"},
{back: "càit a bheil", front: "where is", level: "Home"},
{back: "an toil leibh", front: "do you (formal) like", level: "Home"},
{back: "leabaidh", front: "bed", level: "Home"},
{back: "teine", front: "fire", level: "Home"},
{back: "doras", front: "door", level: "Home"},
{back: "aice", front: "at her", level: "Home"},
{back: "ann an", level: "About Me 2", front: "in"},
{back: "ag obair", level: "About Me 2", front: "working"},
{back: "dùn dè", level: "About Me 2", front: "Dundee"},
{back: "Sruighlea", level: "About Me 2", front: "Stirling"},
{back: "Sealtainn", level: "About Me 2", front: "Shetland"},
{back: "sgoil", level: "About Me 2", front: "school"},
{back: "obair", level: "About Me 2", front: "work"},
{back: "a' fuireach", level: "About Me 2", front: "living"},
{back: "Obar dheathain", level: "About Me 2", front: "Aberdeen"},
{back: "Arcaibh", level: "About Me 2", front: "Orkney"},
{back: "glè mhòr", level: "About Me 2", front: "very big"},
{back: "ospadal", level: "About Me 2", front: "hospital"},
{back: "oilthigh", level: "About Me 2", front: "University"},
{back: "Inbhir àir", level: "About Me 2", front: "Ayr"},
{back: "Peairt", level: "About Me 2", front: "Perth"},
{back: "Port rìgh", level: "About Me 2", front: "Portree"},
{back: "muga", level: "About Me 2", front: "mug"},
{back: "baile", level: "About Me 2", front: "town"},
{back: "Fìobha", level: "About Me 2", front: "Fife"},
{back: "Astràilia", level: "About Me 2", front: "Australia"},
{back: "Afraga a deas", level: "About Me 2", front: "South Africa"},
{back: "Nirribhidh", level: "About Me 2", front: "Norway"},
{back: "an seo", level: "About Me 2", front: "here"},
{back: "an sin", level: "About Me 2", front: "there"},
{back: "Sealainn nuadh", level: "About Me 2", front: "New Zealand"},
{back: "Iapan", level: "About Me 2", front: "Japan"},
{back: "aice", level: "About Me 2", front: "at her"},
{back: "Uibhist", level: "About Me 2", front: "Uist"},
{back: "bùth", level: "About Me 2", front: "Shop"},
{back: "oifis", level: "About Me 2", front: "office"},
{back: "margadh", level: "About Me 2", front: "Market"},
{back: "taigh-òsta", level: "About Me 2", front: "Hotel"},
{back: "Tiriodh", level: "About Me 2", front: "Tiree"},
{back: "meal do naidheachd", level: "Phrases 3", front: "Congratulations"},
{back: "deoch", level: "Phrases 3", front: "Drink"},
{back: "ist", level: "Phrases 3", front: "shush"},
{back: "tha gàidhlig agam", level: "Phrases 3", front: "I have Gaelic"},
{back: "a bheil gàidhlig agad", level: "Phrases 3", front: "Do you speak Gaelic"},
{back: "tha beagan gàidhlig agam", level: "Phrases 3", front: "I have some Gaelic"},
{back: "tha fios agam", level: "Phrases 3", front: "I know"},
{back: "chan eil fios agam", level: "Phrases 3", front: "I do not know"},
{back: "sibh", level: "Phrases 3", front: "you (pl, formal)"},
{back: "chì mi a-rithist thu", level: "Phrases 3", front: "i'll see you again"},
{back: "a h-uile duine", level: "Phrases 3", front: "Everyone"},
{back: "thig a-steach", level: "Phrases 3", front: "come in"},
{back: "m' eudail", level: "Phrases 3", front: "my dear"},
{back: "chì", level: "Phrases 3", front: "can see"},
{back: "agaibh", level: "Phrases 3", front: "at you (pl)"},
{back: "mealaibh ur naidheachd", level: "Phrases 3", front: "congratulations (pl, formal)"},
{back: "eairdsidh", level: "Phrases 3", front: "Archie"},
{back: "oighrig", level: "Phrases 3", front: "Effie"},
{back: "a' bruidhinn", level: "Phrases 3", front: "speaking"},
{back: "ag ionnsachadh", level: "Phrases 3", front: "learning"},
{back: "falt", level: "Body", front: "hair"},
{back: "beul", level: "Body", front: "mouth"},
{back: "broilleach", level: "Body", front: "chest"},
{back: "maol", level: "Body", front: "bald"},
{back: "grànda", level: "Body", front: "ugly"},
{back: "ceann", level: "Body", front: "head"},
{back: "aodann", level: "Body", front: "face"},
{back: "tinn", level: "Body", front: "ill"},
{back: "goirt", level: "Body", front: "sore"},
{back: "fallain", level: "Body", front: "healthy"},
{back: "làmh", level: "Body", front: "hand"},
{back: "cluas", level: "Body", front: "ear"},
{back: "sùil", level: "Body", front: "eye"},
{back: "sròn", level: "Body", front: "nose"},
{back: "duine", level: "Body", front: "man, person"},
{back: "goirid", level: "Body", front: "short"},
{back: "druim", level: "Body", front: "back"},
{back: "caol", level: "Body", front: "narrow"},
{back: "cas", level: "Body", front: "steep"},
{back: "teanga", level: "Body", front: "tongue"},
{back: "falt liath", level: "Body", front: "gray hair"},
{back: "falt ruadh", level: "Body", front: "red hair"},
{back: "falt bàn", level: "Body", front: "blond hair"},
{back: "glan", level: "Body", front: "clean"},
{back: "salach", level: "Body", front: "dirty"},
{back: "air", level: "Body", front: "on"},
{back: "oirre", level: "Body", front: "on her"},
{back: "dubh", level: "Animals", front: "black"},
{back: "ialtag", level: "Animals", front: "bat"},
{back: "staidhre", level: "Animals", front: "Staircase"},
{back: "eaglais", level: "Animals", front: "church"},
{back: "nathair", level: "Animals", front: "a snake"},
{back: "rèis", level: "Animals", front: "race"},
{back: "bò", level: "Animals", front: "a cow"},
{back: "grian", level: "Animals", front: "sun"},
{back: "caileag", level: "Animals", front: "girl"},
{back: "bean", level: "Animals", front: "Wife"},
{back: "piuthar", level: "Animals", front: "sister"},
{back: "gàidhlig", level: "Animals", front: "Gaelic"},
{back: "clach", level: "Animals", front: "a stone"},
{back: "fiacaill", level: "Animals", front: "tooth"},
{back: "feòrag", level: "Animals", front: "Squirrel"},
{back: "feannag", level: "Animals", front: "crow"},
{back: "crùbag", level: "Animals", front: "crab"},
{back: "fuil", level: "Animals", front: "Blood"},
{back: "sràid", level: "Animals", front: "street"},
{back: "sìde", level: "Animals", front: "Weather"},
{back: "slige", level: "Animals", front: "a shell"},
{back: "ceart", level: "Names", front: "right"},
{back: "ceàrr", level: "Names", front: "wrong"},
{back: "Catrìona", level: "Names", front: "Catriona"},
{back: "coibhneil", level: "Names", front: "kind"},
{back: "càirdeil", level: "Names", front: "friendly"},
{back: "Eubha", level: "Names", front: "Eve"},
{back: "Mairead", level: "Names", front: "Margaret"},
{back: "inntinneach", level: "Names", front: "interesting"},
{back: "annasach", level: "Names", front: "unusual"},
{back: "Ealasaid", level: "Names", front: "Elizabeth"},
{back: "Leagsaidh", level: "Names", front: "Lexy"},
{back: "Flòraidh", level: "Names", front: "Flora"},
{back: "pòsta", level: "Names", front: "married"},
{back: "còmhla ri", level: "Hobbies", front: "along with"},
{back: "a' leughadh", level: "Hobbies", front: "reading"},
{back: "a' sgrìobhadh", level: "Hobbies", front: "writing"},
{back: "faisg air", level: "Hobbies", front: "close to"},
{back: "an-dè", level: "Hobbies", front: "yesterday"},
{back: "litir", level: "Hobbies", front: "letter"},
{back: "a' coiseachd", level: "Hobbies", front: "walking"},
{back: "a' ruith", level: "Hobbies", front: "running"},
{back: "leabharlann", level: "Hobbies", front: "library"},
{back: "a-raoir", level: "Hobbies", front: "last night"},
{back: "a' snàmh", level: "Hobbies", front: "swimming"},
{back: "a' cadal", level: "Hobbies", front: "sleeping"},
{back: "a-riamh", level: "Hobbies", front: "ever"},
{back: "a' dol", level: "Hobbies", front: "going"},
{back: "feasgar an-dè", level: "Hobbies", front: "yesterday afternoon"},
{back: "madainn an-dè", level: "Hobbies", front: "yesterday morning"},
{back: "a' seinn", level: "Hobbies", front: "Singing"},
{back: "a' sreap", level: "Hobbies", front: "climbing"},
{back: "màrtainn", level: "Hobbies", front: "Martin"},
{back: "tuathanas", level: "Hobbies", front: "farm"},
{back: "drochaid", level: "Hobbies", front: "bridge"},
{back: "còmhla", level: "Hobbies", front: "together"},
{back: "a' tighinn", level: "Travel", front: "coming"},
{back: "trèana", level: "Travel", front: "Train"},
{back: "plèana", level: "Travel", front: "plane"},
{back: "bus", level: "Travel", front: "bus"},
{back: "stèisean", level: "Travel", front: "station"},
{back: "trèanaichean", level: "Travel", front: "railways"},
{back: "busaichean", level: "Travel", front: "buses"},
{back: "bàta", level: "Travel", front: "boat"},
{back: "càr", level: "Travel", front: "car"},
{back: "a' falbh", level: "Travel", front: "leaving"},
{back: "daor", level: "Travel", front: "expensive"},
{back: "saor", level: "Travel", front: "cheap"},
{back: "dìreach", level: "Travel", front: "just"},
{back: "falbh", level: "Travel", front: "leave"},
{back: "eilean", level: "Travel", front: "island"},
{back: "uinneag", level: "Travel", front: "Window"},
{back: "stad", level: "Travel", front: "stop"},
{back: "tiogaid", level: "Travel", front: "ticket"},
{back: "airgead", level: "Travel", front: "Money"},
{back: "seall air", level: "Travel", front: "Look at"},
{back: "fosgailte", level: "Travel", front: "open"},
{back: "dùinte", level: "Travel", front: "closed"},
{back: "an t-eilean sgitheanach", level: "Travel", front: "Isle of Skye"},
{back: "a' draibheadh", level: "Travel", front: "driving"},
{back: "cudromach", level: "Names 2", front: "important"},
{back: "bochd", level: "Names 2", front: "poor"},
{back: "a sheumais", level: "Names 2", front: "james (vocative)"},
{back: "a chaluim", level: "Names 2", front: "Calum (vocative)"},
{back: "a phàdraig", level: "Names 2", front: "Patrick (vocative)"},
{back: "a thormoid", level: "Names 2", front: "Norman (vocative)"},
{back: "Tormod", level: "Names 2", front: "Norman"},
{back: "Pàdraig", level: "Names 2", front: "Peter"},
{back: "Uilleam", level: "Names 2", front: "William"},
{back: "Uilleim", level: "Names 2", front: "William (vocative)"},
{back: "Aonghas", level: "Names 2", front: "Angus"},
{back: "Aonghais", level: "Names 2", front: "Angus (vocative)"},
{back: "Eòghann", level: "Names 2", front: "Ewan"},
{back: "Eòghainn", level: "Names 2", front: "Ewan (vocative)"},
{back: "Ruairidh", level: "Names 2", front: "Rory"},
{back: "a ruairidh", level: "Names 2", front: "Rory (vocative)"},
{back: "Niall", level: "Names 2", front: "Neil"},
{back: "slaodach", level: "Names 2", front: "slow"},
{back: "a nèill", level: "Names 2", front: "Neil (vocative)"},
{back: "Fionnlagh", level: "Names 2", front: "Finlay"},
{back: "Fhionnlaigh", level: "Names 2", front: "Finlay (vocative)"},
{back: "Frìseal", level: "Names 2", front: "Fraser"},
{back: "a fhrìseil", level: "Names 2", front: "Fraser (vocative)"},
{back: "glic", level: "Names 2", front: "wise"},
{back: "Fearghas", level: "Names 2", front: "Fergus"},
{back: "Fhearghais", level: "Names 2", front: "Fergus (vocative)"},
{back: "greas ort", level: "Feelings 2", front: "hurry up"},
{back: "mise", level: "Feelings 2", front: "me (emphatic)"},
{back: "bòidheach", level: "Feelings 2", front: "beautiful"},
{back: "làidir", level: "Feelings 2", front: "strong"},
{back: "lag", level: "Feelings 2", front: "weak"},
{back: "acras", level: "Feelings 2", front: "hunger"},
{back: "eagal", level: "Feelings 2", front: "fear"},
{back: "oirnn", level: "Feelings 2", front: "on us"},
{back: "thusa", level: "Feelings 2", front: "you (emphatic)"},
{back: "uabhasach", level: "Feelings 2", front: "terrible"},
{back: "sibhse", level: "Feelings 2", front: "you (pl, formal, emphatic)"},
{back: "pathadh", level: "Feelings 2", front: "thirst"},
{back: "fearg", level: "Feelings 2", front: "anger"},
{back: "esan", level: "Feelings 2", front: "he (emphatic)"},
{back: "dragh", level: "Feelings 2", front: "worry"},
{back: "ise", level: "Feelings 2", front: "she (emphatic)"},
{back: "cabhag", level: "Feelings 2", front: "hurry"},
{back: "cnatan", level: "Feelings 2", front: "flu"},
{back: "orra", level: "Feelings 2", front: "on them"},
{back: "oirbh", level: "Feelings 2", front: "on you (plural)"},
{back: "an dèideadh", level: "Feelings 2", front: "toothache"},
{back: "mìcheal", level: "Feelings 2", front: "Michael"},
{back: "gaol", level: "Feelings 2", front: "love"},
{back: "gràin", level: "Feelings 2", front: "hate"},
{back: "A' chuimrigh", level: "Countries", front: "Wales"},
{back: "A' ghearmailt", level: "Countries", front: "Germany"},
{back: "Eilean mhanainn", level: "Countries", front: "Isle of Man"},
{back: "A' phòlainn", level: "Countries", front: "Poland"},
{back: "a' phìob-mhòr", level: "Countries", front: "Bagpipes"},
{back: "Innis tìle", level: "Countries", front: "Iceland"},
{back: "ceòl", level: "Countries", front: "Music"},
{back: "A' bheilg", level: "Countries", front: "Belgium"},
{back: "A' phortagail", level: "Countries", front: "Portugal"},
{back: "ro", level: "Countries", front: "before"},
{back: "clann", level: "Countries", front: "children"},
{back: "craobh", level: "Countries", front: "tree"},
{back: "a' ghrèig", level: "Countries", front: "Greece"},
{back: "An roinn-eòrpa", level: "Countries", front: "Europe"},
{back: "An spàinn", level: "Countries", front: "Spain"},
{back: "An rìoghachd aonaichte", level: "Countries", front: "United Kingdom"},
{back: "An ruis", level: "Countries", front: "Russia"},
{back: "An tuirc", level: "Countries", front: "Turkey"},
{back: "rathad", level: "Countries", front: "Road"},
{back: "An fhraing", level: "Countries", front: "France"},
{back: "An t-suain", level: "Countries", front: "Sweden"},
{back: "A' chòrn", level: "Countries", front: "Cornwall"},
{back: "Breatainn", level: "Countries", front: "Britain"},
{back: "fidheall", level: "Countries", front: "fiddle"},
{back: "fionnlann", level: "Countries", front: "Finland"},
{back: "seacaid", level: "Countries", front: "jacket"},
{back: "An eadailt", level: "Countries", front: "Italy"},
{back: "An ostair", level: "Countries", front: "Austria"},
{back: "An eilbheis", level: "Countries", front: "Switzerland"},
{back: "Sìona", level: "Countries", front: "China"},
{back: "A' bhreatann bheag", level: "Countries", front: "Brittany"},
{back: "abhainn", level: "Countries", front: "river"},
{back: "a-staigh", level: "Pets 2", front: "inside"},
{back: "niseag", level: "Pets 2", front: "Nessy"},
{back: "cat", level: "Pets 2", front: "cat"},
{back: "peata", level: "Pets 2", front: "pet"},
{back: "pàirc", level: "Pets 2", front: "Park"},
{back: "cù", level: "Pets 2", front: "dog"},
{back: "eagalach", level: "Pets 2", front: "scary"},
{back: "each", level: "Pets 2", front: "horse"},
{back: "radan", level: "Pets 2", front: "rat"},
{back: "baga", level: "Pets 2", front: "bag"},
{back: "a-mach", level: "Pets 2", front: "outside"},
{back: "bìodach", level: "Pets 2", front: "tiny"},
{back: "feumail", level: "Pets 2", front: "helpful"},
{back: "coineanach", level: "Pets 2", front: "Rabbit"},
{back: "a-steach", level: "Pets 2", front: "inwards"},
{back: "mathan", level: "Pets 2", front: "bear"},
{back: "tarbh", level: "Pets 2", front: "a bull"},
{back: "broc", level: "Pets 2", front: "badger"},
{back: "gleann", level: "Pets 2", front: "glen"},
{back: "caora", level: "Pets 2", front: "a sheep"},
{back: "eun", level: "Pets 2", front: "a bird"},
{back: "iasg", level: "Pets 2", front: "fish"},
{back: "coille", level: "Pets 2", front: "forest"},
{back: "sligeanach", level: "Pets 2", front: "tortoise"},
{back: "dìleas", level: "Pets 2", front: "loyal"},
{back: "loch", level: "Pets 2", front: "loch"},
{back: "èirisgeidh", level: "Pets 2", front: "Eriskay"},
{back: "a' leum", level: "Pets 2", front: "jumping"},
{back: "gràineag", level: "Pets 2", front: "hedgehog"},
{back: "leòmhann", level: "Pets 2", front: "lion"},
{back: "feur", level: "Pets 2", front: "Grass"},
{back: "mo", level: "Body 2", front: "my"},
{back: "do", level: "Body 2", front: "your"},
{back: "coltach ri", level: "Body 2", front: "similar to"},
{back: "a' coimhead", level: "Body 2", front: "looking"},
{back: "sean", level: "Body 2", front: "old"},
{back: "stamag", level: "Body 2", front: "stomach"},
{back: "tòn", level: "Body 2", front: "bottom"},
{back: "sàbhailte", level: "Body 2", front: "Safe"},
{back: "glùn", level: "Body 2", front: "knee"},
{back: "bodhaig", level: "Body 2", front: "body"},
{back: "gàirdean", level: "Body 2", front: "arm"},
{back: "eadar", level: "Body 2", front: "between"},
{back: "ag èisteachd", level: "Body 2", front: "Listening"},
{back: "briste", level: "Body 2", front: "broken"},
{back: "amhach", level: "Body 2", front: "neck"},
{back: "a' dannsa", level: "Body 2", front: "Dancing"},
{back: "corrag", level: "Body 2", front: "finger"},
{back: "gleansach", level: "Body 2", front: "shiny"},
{back: "bàn", level: "Body 2", front: "fair"},
{back: "ruadh", level: "Body 2", front: "ruadh, ginger"},
{back: "cugallach", level: "Body 2", front: "fragile"},
{back: "diluain", level: "Days", front: "Monday"},
{back: "dimàirt", level: "Days", front: "Tuesday"},
{back: "a' sgioblachadh", level: "Days", front: "tidying"},
{back: "aon-deug", level: "Days", front: "eleven"},
{back: "dà-dheug", level: "Days", front: "twelve"},
{back: "seachd", level: "Days", front: "seven"},
{back: "diciadain", level: "Days", front: "Wednesday"},
{back: "diardaoin", level: "Days", front: "Thursday"},
{back: "trì-deug", level: "Days", front: "thirteen"},
{back: "ceithir-deug", level: "Days", front: "fourteen"},
{back: "còig-deug", level: "Days", front: "fifteen"},
{back: "ag èigheachd", level: "Days", front: "shouting"},
{back: "ochd", level: "Days", front: "eight"},
{back: "dihaoine", level: "Days", front: "Friday"},
{back: "disathairne", level: "Days", front: "Saturday"},
{back: "sia-deug", level: "Days", front: "sixteen"},
{back: "seachd-deug", level: "Days", front: "seventeen"},
{back: "ochd-deug", level: "Days", front: "eighteen"},
{back: "a-màireach", level: "Days", front: "tomorrow"},
{back: "a' feuchainn", level: "Days", front: "trying"},
{back: "Didòmhnaich", level: "Days", front: "Sunday"},
{back: "latha na sàbaid", level: "Days", front: "Sunday (sabbath)"},
{back: "naoi-deug", level: "Days", front: "nineteen"},
{back: "fichead", level: "Days", front: "twenty"},
{back: "a' togail", level: "Days", front: "Building"},
{back: "sinne", level: "Days", front: "we (emphatic)"},
{back: "a-nochd", level: "Days", front: "tonight"},
{back: "iadsan", level: "Days", front: "they (emphatic)"},
{back: "a dh'aithghearr", level: "Days", front: "Soon"},
{back: "air ais", level: "Days", front: "Back"},
{back: "na hearadh", level: "Days", front: "Harris"},
{back: "sàmhach", level: "Days", front: "quiet"},
{back: "seachdain", level: "Days", front: "week"},
{back: "a' coinneachadh", level: "Family 2", front: "Meeting"},
{back: "cuideachail", level: "Family 2", front: "helpful"},
{back: "bràthair", level: "Family 2", front: "brother"},
{back: "pàrant", level: "Family 2", front: "Parent"},
{back: "facal", level: "Family 2", front: "Word"},
{back: "faclair", level: "Family 2", front: "Dictionary"},
{back: "caraid", level: "Family 2", front: "friend"},
{back: "spaideil", level: "Family 2", front: "fancy"},
{back: "teaghlach", level: "Family 2", front: "family"},
{back: "modhail", level: "Family 2", front: "polite"},
{back: "an duine agad", level: "Family 2", front: "Your husband"},
{back: "co-ogha", level: "Family 2", front: "cousin"},
{back: "mìorbhaileach", level: "Family 2", front: "marvellous"},
{back: "mì-mhodhail", level: "Family 2", front: "impolite"},
{back: "seada", level: "Family 2", front: "shed"},
{back: "mo chreach", level: "Family 2", front: "oh goodness"},
{back: "dhachaigh", level: "Family 2", front: "home"},
{back: "mac", level: "Family 2", front: "son"},
{back: "athair", level: "Family 2", front: "father"},
{back: "nighean", level: "Family 2", front: "daughter"},
{back: "doileag", level: "Family 2", front: "doll"},
{back: "seanair", level: "Family 2", front: "grandfather"},
{back: "thalla", level: "Family 2", front: "go away"},
{back: "seanmhair", level: "Family 2", front: "grandmother"},
{back: "beurla", level: "Family 2", front: "English"},
{back: "dèideag", level: "Family 2", front: "toy"},
{back: "taigh-seinnse", level: "Family 2", front: "pub"},
{back: "ball-coise", level: "Sport", front: "football"},
{back: "iomain", level: "Sport", front: "shinty"},
{back: "a h-uile", level: "Sport", front: "every"},
{back: "goilf", level: "Sport", front: "golf"},
{back: "geama", level: "Sport", front: "game"},
{back: "ball", level: "Sport", front: "ball"},
{back: "cunnartach", level: "Sport", front: "dangerous"},
{back: "math air", level: "Sport", front: "good at"},
{back: "rothair", level: "Sport", front: "bike"},
{back: "ag iasgach", level: "Sport", front: "Fishing"},
{back: "deiseil", level: "Sport", front: "ready"},
{back: "a' cluiche", level: "Sport", front: "Playing"},
{back: "tràigh", level: "Sport", front: "beach"},
{back: "teanas", level: "Sport", front: "tennis"},
{back: "a' seòladh", level: "Sport", front: "sailing"},
{back: "rothaireachd", level: "Sport", front: "cycling"},
{back: "rugbaidh", level: "Sport", front: "rugby"},
{back: "an gearasdan", level: "Sport", front: "Fort William"},
{back: "còmhla ri chèile", level: "Sport", front: "together with each other"},
{back: "ball-basgaid", level: "Sport", front: "Basketball"},
{back: "uaireannan", level: "Sport", front: "sometimes"},
{back: "an-dràsta fhèin", level: "Sport", front: "right now"},
{back: "spòrs", level: "Sport", front: "Sport"},
{back: "furasta", level: "Sport", front: "easy"},
{back: "math dhut", level: "Sport", front: "good for you"},
{back: "dannsa gàidhealach", level: "Sport", front: "Highland Dancing"},
{back: "dhut", level: "Sport", front: "to you"},
{back: "doirbh", level: "Sport", front: "Difficult"},
{back: "a' ghàidhealtachd", level: "Sport", front: "The Highlands"},
{back: "a' sgitheadh", level: "Sport", front: "skiing"},
{back: "a' ghalldachd", level: "Sport", front: "The Lowlands"},
{back: "an uairsin", level: "Sport", front: "then"},
{back: "rèidio", level: "Sport", front: "Radio"},
{back: "telebhisean", level: "Sport", front: "Television"},
{back: "milis", level: "Food 3", front: "sweet"},
{back: "searbh", level: "Food 3", front: "bitter"},
{back: "taigh-bìdh", level: "Food 3", front: "restaurant"},
{back: "cidsin", level: "Food 3", front: "kitchen"},
{back: "seòclaid", level: "Food 3", front: "chocolate"},
{back: "am bu toil leat", level: "Food 3", front: "would you like"},
{back: "dinnear", level: "Food 3", front: "Dinner"},
{back: "bracaist", level: "Food 3", front: "breakfast"},
{back: "ith", level: "Food 3", front: "Eat"},
{back: "ceapaire", level: "Food 3", front: "a sandwich"},
{back: "cus", level: "Food 3", front: "too much"},
{back: "aran-milis", level: "Food 3", front: "shortbread"},
{back: "marag-dhubh", level: "Food 3", front: "black pudding"},
{back: "spìosrach", level: "Food 3", front: "spicy"},
{back: "gabh", level: "Food 3", front: "take"},
{back: "a' gabhail", level: "Food 3", front: "taking"},
{back: "bradan", level: "Food 3", front: "salmon"},
{back: "feòil", level: "Food 3", front: "meat"},
{back: "na ith", level: "Food 3", front: "Never eat"},
{back: "na gabh", level: "Food 3", front: "Don't take"},
{back: "measan", level: "Food 3", front: "fruits"},
{back: "glasraich", level: "Food 3", front: "vegetables"},
{back: "truinnsear", level: "Food 3", front: "a plate"},
{back: "is fheàrr leam", level: "Food 3", front: "I prefer"},
{back: "glainne", level: "Food 3", front: "glass"},
{back: "cupa", level: "Food 3", front: "cup"},
{back: "mòr-bhùth", level: "Food 3", front: "Supermarket"},
{back: "albannach", level: "Food 3", front: "Scottish"},
{back: "eadailteach", level: "Food 3", front: "Italian"},
{back: "sìonach", level: "Food 3", front: "Chinese"},
{back: "sgreamhail", level: "Food 3", front: "disgusting"},
{back: "seòclaid theth", level: "Food 3", front: "hot chocolate"},
{back: "dè an uair a tha e", level: "Time", front: "what time is it"},
{back: "uair", level: "Time", front: "hour"},
{back: "dà uair", level: "Time", front: "two o' clock"},
{back: "an dèidh", level: "Time", front: "After"},
{back: "cèilidh", level: "Time", front: "Ceilidh"},
{back: "partaidh", level: "Time", front: "Party"},
{back: "madainn an-diugh", level: "Time", front: "this morning"},
{back: "ma-thà", level: "Time", front: "then (as in 'ok then')"},
{back: "sin", level: "Time", front: "that"},
{back: "uairean", level: "Time", front: "hours"},
{back: "cloc", level: "Time", front: "clock"},
{back: "feasgar an-diugh", level: "Time", front: "this afternoon"},
{back: "boireannach", level: "Time", front: "woman"},
{back: "cuin", level: "Time", front: "when"},
{back: "feasgar a-màireach", level: "Time", front: "tomorrow afternoon"},
{back: "tràth", level: "Time", front: "Early"},
{back: "fadalach", level: "Time", front: "late"},
{back: "sin thu fhèin", level: "Time", front: "there you are"},
{back: "leth uair an dèidh", level: "Time", front: "half past"},
{back: "dà mhionaid", level: "Time", front: "two minutes"},
{back: "madainn a-màireach", level: "Time", front: "tomorrow morning"},
{back: "fichead 's a h-aon", level: "Time", front: "twenty one"},
{back: "fichead 's a dhà", level: "Time", front: "twenty two"},
{back: "fichead 's a...", level: "Time", front: "twenty..."},
{back: "aon uair deug", level: "Time", front: "eleven o'clock"},
{back: "cairteal an dèidh", level: "Time", front: "a quarter after"},
{back: "fichead 's a h-ochd", level: "Time", front: "twenty-eight"},
{back: "coma", level: "Time", front: "indifferent"},
{back: "mionaid", level: "Time", front: "minute"},
{back: "dà uair dheug", level: "Time", front: "twelve o' clock"},
{back: "cairteal gu", level: "Time", front: "quarter to"},
{back: "dè an aois a", level: "Time", front: "How old..."},
{back: "bliadhna", level: "Time", front: "year"},
{back: "am-bliadhna", level: "Time", front: "this year"},
{back: "mìos", level: "Time", front: "month"},
{back: "aois", level: "Time", front: "Age"},
{back: "turadh", level: "Weather 2", front: "dry spell"},
{back: "gu dearbh", level: "Weather 2", front: "indeed"},
{back: "tioram", level: "Weather 2", front: "dry"},
{back: "oidhche", level: "Weather 2", front: "night"},
{back: "gealach", level: "Weather 2", front: "moon"},
{back: "deagh", level: "Weather 2", front: "Good"},
{back: "soilleir", level: "Weather 2", front: "Clear"},
{back: "clachan-meallain", level: "Weather 2", front: "hailstones"},
{back: "reòite", level: "Weather 2", front: "frozen"},
{back: "a' fàs", level: "Weather 2", front: "Growing"},
{back: "caran", level: "Weather 2", front: "somewhat"},
{back: "dìle", level: "Weather 2", front: "flooding"},
{back: "droch", level: "Weather 2", front: "bad"},
{back: "a' cur", level: "Weather 2", front: "putting / falling (weather)"},
{back: "deigh", level: "Weather 2", front: "ice"},
{back: "bog fliuch", level: "Weather 2", front: "soaking wet"},
{back: "cuir", level: "Weather 2", front: "put"},
{back: "sgrathail", level: "Weather 2", front: "disgraceful"},
{back: "feasgar", level: "Weather 2", front: "afternoon"},
{back: "mhadainn", level: "Weather 2", front: "morning"},
{back: "suas", level: "Weather 2", front: "up"},
{back: "àite", level: "Weather 2", front: "place"},
{back: "latha", level: "Weather 2", front: "day"},
{back: "ciùin", level: "Weather 2", front: "calm"},
{back: "miotagan", level: "Weather 2", front: "gloves"},
{back: "a' mheanbh-chuileag", level: "Weather 2", front: "the midgies"},
{back: "sìos", level: "Weather 2", front: "down"},
{back: "muir", level: "Weather 2", front: "Sea"},
{back: "adhar", level: "Weather 2", front: "air"},
{back: "trom", level: "Home 2", front: "heavy"},
{back: "aotrom", level: "Home 2", front: "Light"},
{back: "seòmar", level: "Home 2", front: "room"},
{back: "togalach", level: "Home 2", front: "A building"},
{back: "forca", level: "Home 2", front: "fork"},
{back: "faigh", level: "Home 2", front: "get"},
{back: "peann", level: "Home 2", front: "pen"},
{back: "spàin", level: "Home 2", front: "spoon"},
{back: "làr", level: "Home 2", front: "floor"},
{back: "fada air falbh", level: "Home 2", front: "far away"},
{back: "na tog", level: "Home 2", front: "Do not pick up"},
{back: "tog", level: "Home 2", front: "pick up"},
{back: "flùr", level: "Home 2", front: "flour"},
{back: "taigh", level: "Home 2", front: "house"},
{back: "fear", level: "Home 2", front: "one (masc)"},
{back: "tè", level: "Home 2", front: "one (fem)"},
{back: "mòra", level: "Home 2", front: "big (plural)"},
{back: "beaga", level: "Home 2", front: "small (plural)"},
{back: "dè", level: "Home 2", front: "what"},
{back: "rud", level: "Home 2", front: "thing"},
{back: "thoir dhomh", level: "Home 2", front: "give me"},
{back: "ùra", level: "Home 2", front: "new (plural)"},
{back: "dearga", level: "Home 2", front: "red (plural)"},
{back: "beò", level: "Home 2", front: "alive"},
{back: "marbh", level: "Home 2", front: "dead"},
{back: "siud", level: "Home 2", front: "that over there"},
{back: "matha", level: "Home 2", front: "good (plural)"},
{back: "nurs", level: "Work", front: "nurse"},
{back: "dotair", level: "Work", front: "doctor"},
{back: "tidsear", level: "Work", front: "Teacher"},
{back: "glanadair", level: "Work", front: "cleaner"},
{back: "a' glanadh", level: "Work", front: "cleaning"},
{back: "poileas", level: "Work", front: "Police"},
{back: "a' teagasg", level: "Work", front: "Teaching"},
{back: "banca", level: "Work", front: "bank"},
{back: "ollamh", level: "Work", front: "Professor"},
{back: "colaiste", level: "Work", front: "College"},
{back: "iasgair", level: "Work", front: "fisherman"},
{back: "tuathanach", level: "Work", front: "a farmer"},
{back: "rùnaire", level: "Work", front: "Secretary"},
{back: "a' suidhe", level: "Work", front: "Sitting"},
{back: "sam bith", level: "Work", front: "Any"},
{back: "a' seasamh", level: "Work", front: "Standing"},
{back: "neach-ciùil", level: "Work", front: "musician"},
{back: "neach-bùtha", level: "Work", front: "shopkeeper"},
{back: "neach-frithealaidh", level: "Work", front: "waitor"},
{back: "an siud", level: "Work", front: "over there"},
{back: "croit", level: "Work", front: "Croft"},
{back: "croitear", level: "Work", front: "crofter"},
{back: "a' sabaid", level: "Work", front: "fighting"},
{back: "sagart", level: "Work", front: "priest"},
{back: "ministear", level: "Work", front: "Minister"},
{back: "neach-smàlaidh", level: "Work", front: "firefighter"},
{back: "feòladair", level: "Work", front: "butcher"},
{back: "ge-tà", level: "Work", front: "however, though"},
{back: "ailtire", level: "Work", front: "An architect"},
{back: "còcaire", level: "Work", front: "Cook"},
{back: "clachair", level: "Work", front: "mason"},
{back: "comasach", level: "Work", front: "possible"},
{back: "dìcheallach", level: "Work", front: "hardworking"},
{back: "leisg", level: "Work", front: "lazy"},
{back: "ceist", level: "Work", front: "Question"},
{back: "fad an latha", level: "Work", front: "all day"},
{back: "a' còcaireachd", level: "Work", front: "Cooking"},
{back: "is math sin", level: "Sayings", front: "that's good"},
{back: "làn", level: "Sayings", front: "full"},
{back: "falamh", level: "Sayings", front: "empty"},
{back: "cat-fiadhaich", level: "Sayings", front: "wildcat"},
{back: "seas", level: "Sayings", front: "stand "},
{back: "suidh", level: "Sayings", front: "sit"},
{back: "b' àill leibh", level: "Sayings", front: "pardon?"},
{back: "cathair", level: "Sayings", front: "City"},
{back: "leisgeadair", level: "Sayings", front: "lazy person"},
{back: "fiadh", level: "Sayings", front: "deer"},
{back: "stiall ort", level: "Sayings", front: "on you go"},
{back: "fileanta", level: "Sayings", front: "fluent"},
{back: "foighidneach", level: "Sayings", front: "patient"},
{back: "sgarbh", level: "Sayings", front: "cormorant "},
{back: "ròn", level: "Sayings", front: "seal"},
{back: "bodach", level: "Sayings", front: "old man"},
{back: "cailleach", level: "Sayings", front: "old woman"},
{back: "cruaidh", level: "Sayings", front: "hard"},
{back: "bàrd", level: "Sayings", front: "Bard"},
{back: "sona", level: "Sayings", front: "happy"},
{back: "coltach", level: "Sayings", front: "similar"},
{back: "rudeigin", level: "Sayings", front: "something"},
{back: "cuideigin", level: "Sayings", front: "someone"},
{back: "bog", level: "Sayings", front: "soft"},
{back: "iarann", level: "Sayings", front: "iron"},
{back: "lofa", level: "Sayings", front: "loaf"},
{back: "sionnach", level: "Sayings", front: "Fox"},
{back: "seann", level: "Sayings", front: "old"},
{back: "iongantach", level: "Sayings", front: "amazing"},
{back: "mil", level: "Sayings", front: "honey"},
{back: "ball iomain", level: "Sayings", front: "shinty ball"},
{back: "geàrr", level: "Sayings", front: "Short"},
{back: "seilcheig", level: "Sayings", front: "a snail"},
{back: "seòlta", level: "Sayings", front: "cunning"},
{back: "deònach", level: "Languages", front: "willing"},
{back: "bruidhinn", level: "Languages", front: "Talk"},
{back: "ceap breatainn", level: "Languages", front: "Cape Breton"},
{back: "fraingis", level: "Languages", front: "French"},
{back: "rium", level: "Languages", front: "with me"},
{back: "taingeil", level: "Languages", front: "grateful"},
{back: "èist", level: "Languages", front: "Listen"},
{back: "gàidhlig na h-èireann", level: "Languages", front: "Irish Gaelic"},
{back: "gearmailtis", level: "Languages", front: "German"},
{back: "cànan", level: "Languages", front: "Language"},
{back: "riut", level: "Languages", front: "with you"},
{back: "ribh", level: "Languages", front: "with you (pl, formal)"},
{back: "èistibh", level: "Languages", front: "listen (pl, formal)"},
{back: "ionnsaich", level: "Languages", front: "Learn"},
{back: "a’ bheurla ghallda", level: "Languages", front: "Scots"},
{back: "ris", level: "Languages", front: "with him"},
{back: "cuimris", level: "Languages", front: "Welsh"},
{back: "còrnais", level: "Languages", front: "Cornish"},
{back: "cànan soidhnidh bhreatainn", level: "Languages", front: "British Sign Language"},
{back: "ionnsaichibh", level: "Languages", front: "learn (pl, formal)"},
{back: "rithe", level: "Languages", front: "with her"},
{back: "càirdeach", level: "Languages", front: "related"},
{back: "spainntis", level: "Languages", front: "Spanish"},
{back: "ceilteach", level: "Languages", front: "Celtic"},
{back: "gàidhlig mhanainn", level: "Languages", front: "Manx Gaelic"},
{back: "cànan-soidhnidh aimearaga", level: "Languages", front: "American Sign Language"},
]